so we're just
finishing I have to
stop in 15 we go to
QA we didn't have
any yeah okay yeah yeah we'll do we'll
do 15 minutes and
then yesterday I taught you and I'll
give
yog
word there's two
translation there's the
earlyod
later they started
Tois
word
word for
yog can do all the
different
one
way
owe we will
continue
I
madees we are going through
those get into
it really
is what we learn in the
monter how to
doog we're gonna
start's
theate
thousand there or S
[Music]
me last
I'm
deep so if you don't come you're a
loser yeah and it's online and if you
want you can come little bit in in
person also if you
want
are you can do all your yoga
my classes in we have many other
classes
understand you don't have to learn
hundreds of
practi
you can just do
one if you
[Music]
understand one the greatest Pres
two
months University doesn't give me too
much work
[Music]
okay
two
is to think about that every human
being right to
happiness
ruin
all
Liv everyone
equ
dos snakes
rattlesnakes you believe in equal
rights you
will
are
country equal
if your income is very low you support
the rich countri
should
if suffering people
streng youry where
your I'm
[Music]
very
refes they go
to Refugee after one or two
years
we are
suppor
[Music]
what's it
called famous Cosmetics
company bubble bubble but they were so
to
L estate louder yeah so
anyway we to
fundrais
tried to get funds for
the and we had to go the day
before whenever I go to New York I stay
at John's
don't
know
real exective and he had one
of
and a few years later someone gave
him so so we went home and we're really
tired
I said he said let's go to
bed he had two rooms and he had
a
fruit then I there's two Asian
Ladi
where you
guys
wow get a what do you call
Visa you don't
havep what's it like you know she said
well it's very strange because we
have refugee
camp this is all in English
right I didn't say
anything
so how did you get a Visa they
said learn programing computer center
and then we
got
they said those guys
save I went outside I'm
crying what do you call SP in
mexo and then we
beauti
yeah generally people don't help
refes
there feeling when you
help of your money
right to
it you must give it to
them you you
got
equ
inome
share what you
have it's not yours
really somebody
else
me okay
really
don't my okay last
story it's for a
dog it's a dog
Bell he runs me he will ring the
bell
he he he he rings the bell you know he
says he says you know get out here quick
get what was the
story no that's something
else
never
mind
huh no but why he ring the
bell you know all the
stories that's
it uh so he rang the bell
Christi Pop came to New York
City at that moment I don't
know give your
extra
give half of everything don't give 2%
don't
yes that's what
this to
all right